preciousglow.com 2008-06-22

# Privacy Policy - Wedding Rings, Anniversary Bands, Diamond Jewelry, Engagement Ring

Preciousglow.com will occasionally update its privacy statement to reflect company and customer feedback. When Preciousglow.com posts changes to this statement, you will see the word "Updated" next to the Privacy Policy link on the Preciousglow.com home page. Preciousglow.com encourages you to periodically review this page to be informed of how we are protecting your information. If you have questions or concerns about policy changes, you should first contact the Preciousglow.com customer service department at [service@Preciousglow.com](mailto:service@Preciousglow.com) or **866-441-1278**.

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy is designed to inform you of what information Preciousglow.com collects, why we collect such information and how we use the information we collect.

 **Collection And Use Of Information**   
In general, you can browse our Web Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. Personally identifiable information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name; home, billing or other physical address; an email address; phone number or other contact information; and a credit card number and expiration date. When you submit your personally identifiable information to us, you are giving us your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information as set forth in this privacy policy.

As a policy, Preciousglow.com does not sell, trade or rent your personally identifiable information to third-parties, unless you have granted us permission to do so.

 **Communications :** If you provide Preciousglow.com with personally identifiable information, this information may be used to communicate to you information regarding Preciousglow.com and its products and services. For example, we may communicate to you information regarding promotions, surveys, contests, sweepstakes or product or service updates. Your personally identifiable information may also be used to improve and customize our Web Site's content, layout and services. These uses improve and customize our interactions with you to better meet your needs.

In addition to the uses set forth above, if you contact one of our diamond and jewelry consultants (and provide personally identifiable information to the consultant) or submit a request or inquiry through our Web Site, we will use your information to respond to your inquiry or request and to provide you with any other additional information that we believe may be helpful or interesting to you. 

If you place an order with Preciousglow.com, in addition to the uses set forth above, we will use your personally identifiable information to confirm your order, prevent and detect fraud or abuse, respond to your requests or inquiries, provide you with other administrative information regarding your order and provide you with any other information we deem helpful or interesting to you. 

If you do not want to receive communications from Preciousglow.com you may elect to opt-out of receiving such communications; please see the "Choice/Opt-Out" section below for more information.

 **Internal Use :** We may compare and review your personally identifiable information for errors, omissions and accuracy. We may also use your personally identifiable information internally to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, Web Site content and product offerings. Your personally identifiable information may also be used internally to conduct internal research on our users' demographics, interests, behavior and generally to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of our Web Site and our marketing programs.

 **Compliance with Law and Fraud Protection :** We may collect and disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. We may collect and possibly share personally identifiable information and any other information available to us in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any personal or as otherwise required by law. We may also exchange information, including personally identifiable information, with other companies and organizations for credit fraud protection and risk reduction.

 **Service Providers :** We may share your personally identifiable information with authorized third party partners, agents and contractors. For example, if we need to ship something to you, we must share your name and address with a shipping company. Examples of other third parties that we may share your personal information with include: webhosting companies, fulfillment companies (e.g., companies that fulfill product orders), jewelers, assemblers, data analysis firms, affiliates, third party consulting or marketing firms and e-mail service providers. Additionally, if you use a credit card or other financing alternative to place an order with Preciousglow.com, to confirm and process your order we will share your personally identifiable information with such financing company. These third parties only receive personally identifiable information if such information is needed to perform their function(s), and they are not authorized to use any personally identifiable information for any other purpose(s) other than the purpose(s) set forth by Preciousglow.com. We only provide third-parties with the minimum amount of personally identifiable information necessary to complete the requested service, product or transaction.

 **Special Events :** If you choose to participate in a special event (for example, a promotion, contest or sweepstake), Preciousglow.com may share your personally identifiable information with those organizations participating in the applicable event. Typically, these third parties do not use your information for any other purpose other than to manage the event. In some cases these third-party partners may send you promotional materials regarding their products and services. In these cases, you will be given the opportunity to opt-out, and not have your personally identifiable information shared with that third-party partner.

If at any time you choose to enter a Preciousglow.com feedback contest and allow us to post your feedback on our Web Site, we will remove your feedback from our Web Site at any time if you send your request via e-mail to [service@Preciousglow.com](mailto:service@Preciousglow.com). Send this Product to a Friend: When you e-mail a product to a friend, you and your friend's names and e-mail addresses are requested. This ensures that your friend will know that you have requested that Preciousglow.com send them an e-mail. You and your friend's e-mail addresses will only be used for this purpose unless permission is otherwise granted.

 **Refer a Friend :** Using a Preciousglow.com form, you can also refer a friend to the Preciousglow.com Web Site. You and your friend's names and e-mail addresses are requested to ensure that your friend will know that you have requested that Preciousglow.com send them an e-mail. You and your friend's e-mail addresses will only be used for this purpose unless permission is otherwise granted. 

**Business Transfer :** Your personally identifiable information may be disclosed as part of any merger, sale of company assets or acquisition, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, in which personally identifiable information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the Company. International Transfers: Information collected on this Web Site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Preciousglow.com or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities and by using this Web Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

Preciousglow.com abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of data from the European Union.

 **IP Address :** When you visit our Web Site, Preciousglow.com collects your IP address to, among other things, help diagnose problems with its server, administer and tune the operation of its Web Site, analyze trends, track traffic patterns, gather demographic information for aggregate use, and track the date and duration of each session within our Web Site. Your IP address may also be used in combination with your personally identifiable information for credit fraud protection and risk reduction.

 **Data Collection Devices, such as Cookies and Web Beacons :** In some instances, Preciousglow.com may collect non-personal data through cookies, web logs, web beacons (also know as pixel gifs or action tags) and other monitoring technologies. Where authorized by us, third parties may use cookies, Preciousglow.com's web log files, web beacons and other monitoring technologies to compile aggregate statistics on Preciousglow.com's behalf. The non-personal information that we collect is used to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of our Web Site and marketing programs. We may share or transfer non-personally identifiable information with or to our affiliates, licensees and partners.

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies on certain pages of our Web Site to, among other things, analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, deliver you a more customized shopping experience, track visits from our affiliates and partners and allow the use of our shopping cart. Preciousglow.com does not use cookies to store or collect any personally identifiable information. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits; although, by declining the use of cookies you may not be able to use certain features on the Web Site.

Preciousglow.com Web pages may also contain electronic images know as Web beacons. These Web beacons allow Preciousglow.com to count users who have visited certain Web pages or to deliver co-branded services. Preciousglow.com may also include Web beacons in its email messages in order to determine whether the message has been opened or acted upon. 

Additionally, Preciousglow.com may use third-party advertising or content delivery companies to serve ads or images on our Web Site or on other web sites on the World Wide Web. These companies may use web beacons to place a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows the third party to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compiles anonymous information. Information collected through these third-party advertising companies is anonymous.

 **Children Under 13**  
Preciousglow.com does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that data from our systems. Please visit the FTC's website at [www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/) for tips on protecting children's privacy online.

 **Links**  
Our Web Site may provide links to other third-party Web Sites which are outside our control and not covered by this privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) Web Sites.

 **Security**  
Preciousglow.com is committed to the protection of the personally identifiable information that you share with us. We utilize a combination of security technologies, procedures and organizational measures to help protect your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For example, we store the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers with limited access. Additionally, when we transfer sensitive personal information (for example, credit card information) over the Internet, we protect it using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology.

 **Updating Your Information**  
If the personally identifiable information Preciousglow.com has gathered from you changes or you would like to revise such information, we will gladly correct or update any personal data you have previously provided to us. To request a change or update to your personal information, please send an e-mail to [service@Preciousglow.com](mailto:service@Preciousglow.com) or contact one of our diamond and jewelry consultants at **866-441-1278**.

 **Choice / Opt-Out**  
We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. To opt-out of receiving communications from Preciousglow.com: (1) select "unsubscribe" on our subscription status page and enter the requested information; or (2) make your request in person by contacting a diamond and jewelry consultant at **866-441-1278** or by e-mail at [service@Preciousglow.com](mailto:service@Preciousglow.com).

 **Your Consent To Preciousglow.com Privacy Policy**  
By using this Web Site, you agree to Preciousglow.com's privacy policy. This is our entire and exclusive privacy policy and it supersedes any earlier version. We may occasionally update this privacy policy. When a revision is made we will revise the "last updated" date on this page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy policy to stay informed about how we are protecting your information. Your continued use of this Web Site constitutes your consent to this privacy policy and any updates.

For other terms and conditions that apply to your use of our Web Site, please see our Preciousglow.com Product Policies and Legal Notices.

 **Questions Or Comments**  
If you have questions about this privacy policy, please contact the Preciousglow.com customer service department at [service@Preciousglow.com](mailto:service@Preciousglow.com) or at **866-441-1278**. You may also send us your comments about the Preciousglow.com Web Site or the shopping experience in general, as we always appreciate feedback .
